{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800424542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800424542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800424806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800424805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800428745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800428745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800428984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800428984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800432889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800432889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_osha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800433146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800433145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_osha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800436573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800436573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800437119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800437119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800442921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800442921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800443434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800443434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800447230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800447230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800447425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800447425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800450811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800450811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ruka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800451056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800451056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ruka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800451860","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800451859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ruka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800454664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800454664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngumi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800455082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800455082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngumi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800460918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800460918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngumi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800466713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800466713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngumi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800467140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800467139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngumi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800473364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800473364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kundi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800474088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800474088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kundi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800480244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800480244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_debe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800480490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800480490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_debe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" be"," userResponse":" be"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800484809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800484809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_uzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800485157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800485157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_uzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800487169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800487168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_uzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800491978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800491978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_uzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.4.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800505056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800505056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_uzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800509226","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800509225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" cb4ee61c-ffb3-4e4e-9ad7-ee967bbd46a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_uzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800520815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800520815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800521410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800521409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800522334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800522333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800522485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800522485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800523204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800523203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800523896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800523895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800524627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800524626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800525211","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800525210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800525450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800525450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800525943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800525942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800529518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800529518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800536101","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800536101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800537965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800537965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" START_HAMISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800538983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800538982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800540630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800540630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800541605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800541605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800542341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800542341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800543257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800543257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800543967","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800543966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800545535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800545534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" START_WALIENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800547239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800547239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800548611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800548611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800549754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800549752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800550439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800550439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800551547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800551547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800551677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800551676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800554572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800554571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800555092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800555092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800555709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800555708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800556527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800556526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800557434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800557434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800560305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800560304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" START_ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800561811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800561811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800563428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800563427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800563440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800563439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800564726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800564726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800568813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800568813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800571093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800571093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800571525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800571525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800571643","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800571642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800572087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800572086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800572603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800572603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800573392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800573391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800574064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800574064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800576054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800576054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800577356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800577356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800577370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800577369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800577385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800577385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800578056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800578056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800579155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800579155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800580999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800580998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800583062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800583062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800585524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800585523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800586210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800586209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800587343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800587342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800587887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800587886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800588084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800588084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800588727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800588726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800589659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800589659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800590452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800590450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800591148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800591148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800597051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800597051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800597641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800597641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800601064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800601064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" START_NINUNULIE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800605239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800605238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800606310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800606310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800606313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800606313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800606317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800606317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800608596","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800608596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800610646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800610645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800613033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800613033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800615310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800615309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800616373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800616373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800617155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800617154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800617325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800617324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800617759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800617759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800618837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800618837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800620053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800620053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800620810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800620809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800622413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800622412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800623141","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800623140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" START_NINANUNUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800624065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800624065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800625809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800625808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800626118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800626117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800628982","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800628982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800630577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800630577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800630951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800630951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800631854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800631853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800638491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800638491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800640158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800640157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" START_ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800642000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800642000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800644291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800644290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800644649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800644649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800645426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800645425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800645788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800645788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800646441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800646441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800646982","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800646982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800647337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800647337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800647842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800647841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800648706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800648705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800649431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800649430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800649959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800649958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800651889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800651889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800653325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800653324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800656124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800656123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800657419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800657418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800658635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800658634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800659947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800659946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" START_SHATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800661998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800661998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800663730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800663730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800665848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800665848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800667503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800667503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" START_SINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800669330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800669330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800672699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800672699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800677291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800677291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800680095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800680095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800682837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800682837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800683857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800683856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800684092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800684091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800684658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800684657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800685941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800685941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800686395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800686395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800687150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800687149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800687691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800687690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800687861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800687860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800688483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800688482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800689362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800689361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800692918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800692917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" START_LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800693892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800693891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800694559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800694559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800694669","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800694669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800699775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800699775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 50a5aa13-d069-4e3f-9295-5163d912ec61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800709369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800709368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800710415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800710415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800713183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800713183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800714817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800714817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800717845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800717845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800718890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800718890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800721814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800721814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800722154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800722153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800723001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800723000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" ZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800724577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800724577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800725647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800725647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800728282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800728282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800731798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800731798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" isha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800732832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800732832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" isha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHA"," userResponse":" ISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800736134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800736134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800736453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800736453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800737277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800737276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hiyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800739871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800739871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hiyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800743418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800743418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hiyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800743480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800743480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hiyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800750527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800750526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 78221e77-fe47-480a-bdda-4308b56cadbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hiyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800762206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800762206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800762829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800762828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800763617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800763616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800764781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800764781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800765236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800765236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800766022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800766022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800768405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800768405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800768550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800768550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800773434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800773434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800779796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800779795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800784190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800784190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800789971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800789971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800795588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800795588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800802128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800802128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800808441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800808441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800814810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800814810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800819924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800819924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800825475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800825475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800832317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800832316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800838389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800838389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800843544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800843544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800849302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800849301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800860709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800860709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800865977","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800865977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800870612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800870611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800876746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800876746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800881556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800881556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800886294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800886294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800890466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800890466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549800896298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549800896297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_150642"," gameId":" 01236fd3-ff64-412a-bfa2-f2db94e9315d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}